RILSANA ZUBAIR

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



CONTACT

+971 58 304 1329

Dubai, UAE

rilzanazubair@gmail.com

in http://linkedin.com/in/rilsana-zubair

EDUCATION

B-Tech in Computer Science

Kerala Technological University 2018-2022

KEY SKILLS

REACT

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

SQL

BOOTSTRAP

MEDIA QUERY

CORE JAVA

MONGO DB

POSTMAN

GITHUB

CAMPUS-RECRUITED INTERNSHIP

- Responsive Web Design
- Full Stack Java

PROFILE

Website developer with a passion for moving the web forward through creativity, innovation & enterprise. Dynamic web developer experienced in producing interactive web applications. Specialize in font-end development and a basic understanding of back-end technology.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Maskan Technologies | MAY 2023 - AUG 2023

- Developed a real estate website using React.js, showcasing offering visitors a visually appealing and efficient platform for browsing.
- Designed E-commerce website from scratch, incorporating essential features with a seamless shopping experience.
- Experience with architecture and scaling of websites, specifically E-commerce sites.
- Familiarity with front-end frameworks such as Bootstrap and React, enabling efficient development and design implementation.
- Designed and implemented database schemas: MongoDB for a social media application allowing profile creation, updates, and interaction.

Web Developer

Technologics | NOV 2022 - MAR 2023

- Developed clones of Netflix and LinkedIn, replicating the user interfaces and layouts to closely resemble the original platforms.
- Designed and coded the user interfaces with meticulous attention to detail, ensuring an authentic visual experience for users
- Writing reusable, testable and efficient code
- Troubleshoot and resolve both hardware and software related problem.